export default [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Why Should I distribute my game on the Epic Games Store?",
    answer:
      "The Epic Games Store has a global audience of over 230M+ users, a 88%/12% revenue split and additional no-cost services to help bring your game to market. For games built on Unreal Engine, engine royalty fees are waived for in-store purchases using Epic's payment processor. In-app purchases and products using their own payment processor are not exempt from engine royalties.",
    ask: false,
  },

  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      "My game is built with Unity or another engine, can I bring i to the Epic Games store?",
    answer:
      "Yes, the Epic Games store is engine-agnostic. Epic is aiming to bring great games to players, regardless of your engine choice.",
    ask: false,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What are the Epic Games Store self-service publishing tools?",
    answer:
      "They are a suite of tools within the Epic Developer Portal used by developers to set up their game pages, pricing, offers, builds, and updates on the Epic Games Store.",
    ask: false,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What is the Epic Developer Portal?",
    answer:
      " The Developer Portal is the central hub to distribute games on the Epic Games Store and enhance games with Epic Online Services. The Developer Portal is used to update product information, configure back-end services, support players, and view game financial data, usage reports, and other statistical data. Learn more by reading the Developer Portal documentation",
    ask: false,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "What other developer tools does Epic offer?",
    answer:
      "Epic offers an ecosystem of tools, services, and communities to help anyone create, power, and distribute software. With a single Epic Games account, anyone can create with Unreal Engine, enhance with Epic Online Services and Kids Web Services, and distribute PC games on the Epic Games Store. Even more tools like Twinmotion, MetaHuman, Quixel, and Capturing Reality bring your project to the next level. And the Epic Developer Community is here to connect creators alike to share and learn. Learn more about Epic's ecosystem of tools, services, and communities.",
    ask: false,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "How do I distribute games on the Epic Games Store?",
    answer:
      " Getting started is easy, just log in or create an account at dev.epicgames.com/portal. From there the sign up wizard will help guide registration of your company and the build of your first game. Be sure to have business information (contact info and tax/payout information) on hand. Important to note there is a recoupable $100 USD submission fee per game which will need to paid before releasing on the store. Read our announcement blog for an overview of the self-publishing process.",
    ask: false,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Are there any requirements for a game to launch on the store",
    answer:
      "All products published on the Epic Games Store adhere to our content guidelines. In addition, they must launch, run, and be consistent with the product description presented to users via their Product Details Page (PDP). Multiplayer games must support crossplay across all PC stores. This is to make sure players who purchase a multiplayer game on any store can easily connect with other players, regardless of where the game was purchased. To achieve this, you can implement crossplay yourself, use a third-party SDK, or use Epic Online Services for free.",
    ask: false,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Any Prohibited content that the Store my decline?",
    answer:
      " Products that contain prohibited content (hateful or discriminatory content, pornography, and illegal content) are not eligible for distribution on the Epic Games Store. Content that infringes on intellectual property you do not own or have rights to use scams, frauds, or deceptive practices, such as fake games or malware are also prohibited. Published products receiving complaints about content that does not meet the criteria may be subject to re-review and removal from the Epic Games Store. Visit the Epic Games Store Ratings & Content Guidelines documentation for more information.",
    ask: false,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Does the Epic Games store have regional pricing?",
    answer:
      "Yes, we do support regional pricing. We also have a set of suggested regional discounts based on local norms.",
    ask: false,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "How do refunds work on the Epic Games store?",
    answer:
      "Games and products purchased through the Epic Games Store are generally eligible for a refund. These products are marked “refundable”. If a game or product is marked as non-refundable, then it is not eligible for a refund. Products that include virtual currency or other consumables are marked “non-refundable” and are not eligible for refund. Also, most in-app purchases are non-refundable. Epic cannot provide refunds for purchases made outside of the Epic Games Store. Visit the Epic Games Store Refund Policy for more information. ",
    ask: false,
  },
];
